https://www.pheasant.com/privacy

MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm site, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm collects personally identifiable information, such as your email
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This
information is used by MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
does not read any of your private online communications.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
and MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm collects and uses your personal information to operate the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm and its affiliates. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm, in order to determine what MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm pages, or
register with MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm site or services, a cookie helps MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact MacFarlane Pheasants - Pheasant Chicks, Mature Birds, America's Largest Pheasant Farm at info@pheasant.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
